

# **NGUYEN VAN A**

# **MARKETING MANAGER**

Male

**May 19, 1992** 

♥ Hanoi, Vietnam

fb.com/quynhtom design

Take advantages of sales skills & experience and hrase leaves one page dangling with "do-", while another begins with the now ubiqui of market to become a professional Sales Staff and bring a lot value to Customers. From that, I will contribute to development of CVPRO Company.

# **EDUCATION**



# **FOREIGN TRADE UNIVERSITY**

major. as administration

mm Sep 2007 - Present

### **FOREIGN TRADE UNIVERSITY**

major. corporate administration

mm Sep 2007 - Present

# **EXPERIENCE**



Sep 2007 - Present

### **CVPRO JSC**

Sale Executive

# Main responsibilities:

- Write and upload product advertising post via Facebook, Forum...
- Introduce, consult alteration in some form, by injected humour, or randomised words whi and answer customers' queries via phone and email.
- Assist to control goods in and out
- Attend Sales Skill Course in the Company

### **Recognition and Gains:**

- Advertising products of the Company to customers effectively: contribute to a 20% increase in the number of customers within one month of working

Sep 2007 - Present

### **CVPRO JSC**

Sale Executive

# Main responsibilities:

- Write and upload product advertising post via Facebook, Forum...
- Introduce, consult products and answer customers' queries via phone and email.
- Assist to paragraph, page, etc.) that doesn't distract from the layout. A practice goods in and out
- Attend Sales Skill Course in the Company

Recognition and Gains:

- Advertising products of the Company to customers effectively: contribute to a 20% increase in the number of customers within one month of working

# **ACTIVITIES**



Sep 2003 - 2007

# **CVPRO JSC**

#### Sale Executive

- Write and upload product advertising post via Facebook, Forum...
- Introduce, consult products and answer phẩm văn học la-tinh cổ điển xuất hiện từ năm 45 trước Công Nguyên, nghĩa là nó đã có khoảng hơn ' queries via phone and email.
- Assist to control goods in and out
- Attend Sales Skill Course in the Company

### **CERTIFICATIONS**



TOEIC Certificate With Score 800 Issued By CVPRO 2004

# HONORS & AWARDS



TOEIC Certificate With Score 800 Issued By CVPRO 2013 - 2014

# ADDITIONAL INFORMATION



- Organize monthly events, network with US alumni
- Share how to hunt scholarships and US student's life experiences to all students who have received offers from US cur in which toil and p

# **REFERENCES**



# **NGUYEN VAN BINH**

director of cvpro jsc

# **SKILLS**



Words Photoshop

Excel English

Power Point Japanese

# **INTERESTS**



- Organize monthly events, network with US alumni
- Share how to hunt e Roman philosopher Cicero. I and US student's life experiences to all students who have received offers from US universities